<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>微服务 on Hugo Book</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/%E5%BE%AE%E6%9C%8D%E5%8A%A1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 微服务 on Hugo Book</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 16:07:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/%E5%BE%AE%E6%9C%8D%E5%8A%A1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SpringCloud</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/serviceGovernance/Springcloud/springCloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 16:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/serviceGovernance/Springcloud/springCloud/</guid>
      <description>参考&#xD;#&#xD;SpringCloud 面试题 （持续更新、吐血推荐）</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpringBoot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/serviceGovernance/Springcloud/springboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 15:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/serviceGovernance/Springcloud/springboot/</guid>
      <description>Core&#xD;#&#xD;Spring Boot定义&#xD;#&#xD;Spring Boot is designed to get you up and running as quickly as possible, with minimal upfront configuration of Spring. Spring Boot takes an opinionated view of building production-ready applications.&#xA;Features (官方)&#xD;#&#xD;Create stand-alone Spring applications Embed Tomcat, Jetty or Undertow directly (no need to deploy WAR files) Provide opinionated &amp;lsquo;starter&amp;rsquo; dependencies to simplify your build configuration Automatically configure Spring and 3rd party libraries whenever possible Provide production-ready features such as metrics, health checks, and externalized configuration Absolutely no code generation and no requirement for XML configuration 特性&#xD;#&#xD;自动配置 Auto Configuration 为Spring及第三方库提供自动配置; 简化了项目的构建配置;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>微服务 总结</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/serviceGovernance/Overview/microservice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 15:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/serviceGovernance/Overview/microservice/</guid>
      <description>目录&#xD;#&#xD;微服务 定义&#xD;#&#xD;In short, the microservice architectural style [1] is an approach to developing a single application as a suite of small services, each running in its own process and communicating with lightweight mechanisms, often an HTTP resource API. These services are built around business capabilities and independently deployable by fully automated deployment machinery. There is a bare minimum of centralized management of these services, which may be written in different programming languages and use different data storage technologies.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
